const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        answer: 'Hypertext Markup Language',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'What does HTML stand for?',
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        answer: '<!DOCTYPE html>',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'What should go at the top of every HTML page?',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        answer: '<html>',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'What is the root element?',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        answer: '<head> and <body>',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'What are the two main grouping elements that sit inside the HTML tags?',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        answer: '<meta>, <title>, <link>, <script>',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'What are some tags you would likely find in the head element?',
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        answer: '<body> inside the body tags </body>',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'Where would you find all of the visible content that shows up on the screen?',
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        answer: 'By using <h1>, <h2>, <h3>, <h4>, <h5>, or <h6> tags',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'How would you create a header?',
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        answer: '<p> tags',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'How would you create a paragraph?',
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        answer: '<ol> and <li> tags',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'How would you make a numbered list?',
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        answer: '<ul> and <li> tags',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'How would you make a bulleted list?',
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        answer: '<table>, <tr>, <th>, and <td>',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'What are the elements you need to build a table?',
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        answer: 'action and method',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'What attributes does a form need?',
    },
    {
        id: 12.5,
        answer: 'method="POST"',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'What method should you use for private or sensitive information, like username and password?',
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        answer: '<input>, <textarea>, <select>',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'What form controls do you have access to for user input?',
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        answer: 'text, email, password, date, number, checkbox, radio, submit, etc.',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'What input types are available to use?',
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        answer: '<img src="..." alt="boat on a lake" />',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'How do you display an image? ',
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        answer: '<a href="https://www.google.com">Google</a>',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'How do you create a link to another site?',
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        answer: '<a href="https://www.google.com" target="_blank">Google</a>',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'How do you open a link in another tab?',
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        answer: '<a href=”https://www.google.com#middle>Middle of google page</a>',
        category: 'HTML',
        question: 'How do you link to a specific section of a page?',
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        answer: 'Cascading style sheet',
        category: 'CSS',
        question: 'What does CSS stand for?',
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        answer: 'p { color: red; }',
        category: 'CSS',
        question: 'How do you select all p tags and color them red?',
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        answer: 'p#first-paragraph {}',
        category: 'CSS',
        question: 'How do you select a p element with an id of ‘first-paragraph’?',
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        answer: 'p.red { color:red; }',
        category: 'CSS',
        question: 'How do you select all p elements with a class of red',
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        answer: 'div p {}',
        category: 'CSS',
        question: 'How do you select a p tag that is inside a div?',
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        answer: 'background-color, color, display, height, width, margin, padding, position, box-sizing, border, border-radius, etc.',
        category: 'CSS',
        question: 'What are some common styles?',
    },
    // {
    //     id: 25,
    //     answer: '',
    //     category: 'CSS',
    //     question: '',
    // },
];

export {questions};